Let's see if you can fight in the dark.
Show me your cat-like abilities.
You really are a shameless woman.
Remember this until the afterlife.
I will never let your soul rest.
Remember that!
In Tagalog,
one bullet is all it takes.
Mikoy.
This is my fight.
Hey, stop, or else I'll really kill you.
Mikoy, don't!
That was fun, wasn't it?
Did you enjoy that, sir?
Are you trying to get yourself killed?
You're being so dramatic.
We were just having fun.
Having fun?
Didn't you see this?
That's not my Adam's apple.
My balls went up here.
Even the eggs I had for breakfast,
I threw them up!
You're so dramatic.
Just get on.
Let's go back to base. Get on.
If you want, you can go by yourself.
I don't want to die yet!
Suit yourself.
Suit yourself, too.
Hey, hey! Where are you going?
Hey!
What are you doing?
Go on! Go!
Fine!
Hey. Hey! Hey!
Come back here!
Hey!
I heard you left our customer
in the middle of nowhere?
Why? What's the problem?
Chiara, I'm talking to you.
What happened?
Are you thinking or doing this on purpose?
Mikoy, we were having
a perfectly good conversation.
What's with all this lovey-dovey stuff?
Huh?
Why? What did my sweetheart do?
Why don't you ask Chiara
how she turned my ATV adventure
into an extreme sport?
What?
Maybe she just turned your adventure
business into a real adventure?
Mikoy, I have no problem with adventure.
But Chiara is different.
Whenever I take her as my tour guide,
I feel like I'm in
a permanent danger zone!
I admit I did go
a little too fast earlier,
but it wasn't my fault!
So whose fault was it?
The ATV you bought was powerful.
So I just unleashed its power
to its full potential.
So it's my fault, Chiara?
It won't happen again.
It was her first time.
What do you mean, first time?
What about what she did the other day?
I guess I can't do this. Sorry.
I'm just going to get off. I'm scared now.
-Oh my God, please. Sorry.
-No. You can do it.
No, I really can't.
I really can't. I'm just going to get off.
Come on. Please? Sorry.
And you know, you know how I'm feeling?
I'm genuinely terrified right now.
Please, let me get off!
It was just that one time, I promise!
It was only that one woman.
She deserved that treatment.
She was annoying.
What about what you did
to my senior citizen companions?
Did they deserve that treatment too?
And who said you could stop?
We need to hurry, don't we?
We need to catch the sunset.
Why did you even hike if you weren't
going to make it to the focal point?
Good grief, girl.
We can't do this anymore.
At this rate, heaven might take us
because of all this suffering.
Well, Grandpa, that's exactly
what's going to happen
if that's what you keep thinking.
If you think you're young and strong,
you will feel young and strong!
Oh, girl!
We don't need to see that sunset anymore.
We don't need it anymore. Bye!
They're so weak! You're all so weak!
Well, I explained everything properly.
I warned them
about what to expect on the hike.
But they insisted.
They insisted, and then they're the ones
who kept complaining!
That attitude of yours is going
to ruin my business!
Don't you know that
the customer is always right?
especially when they're abusive
and ill-mannered.
There.
Sir Pandoy, I'm really sorry.
Let me talk to Chiara.
We coordinated
with the Italian authorities.
But for now,
it seems they're avoiding it.
They don't want the complication
of handling La Morte Bianca's remains.
Her reputation in Italy
is also a sensitive matter.
So we can say that they
don't want it to seem
like they had anything
to do with her death.
But most of them have either been arrested
or are on the run.
But the moment
they cross into another territory,
So is it safe to say
that we have completely dismantled
the Concordat?
This organization is still extensive, sir.
And it's just a matter of time
before new leadership emerges.
Luckily, we managed to freeze
most of their major accounts
while they were asleep,
and we didn't just cripple them. Ouch!
It looks like we paralyzed
their entire organization. Victory!
I'm cute!
But I'm getting more handsome
because I'm part of G.A.G.O!
And as time goes by,
their world keeps getting smaller.
Well, rehabilitation does have
its merits, right?
Especially for people
who have a chance to change.
Like this person.
They say people don't change.
Are you sure about that, Agent Sianong?
If these two mess up again,
I'll personally have them arrested.
That's harsh! Come on, chill!
Agent Alex, it's like our history
means nothing to you!
They are currently in our custody.
Their lawyers are appealing
for mitigating circumstances,
arguing that, in the end,
they helped dismantle
the Concordat and La Morte Bianca.
They might have other information
that they can provide
in exchange for other leads.
Information that may still be held
by the loose elements
of the Concordat and La Morte Bianca.
And what did they say?
They said they had nothing else to offer.
Or they don't want to talk anymore
because they've lost their power,
and their lives will be in danger.
Not that one.
The elephant I'm talking about
is Mikoy and Chiara.
Where are Mikoy and Chiara?
Sir Pandoy is wrong
because the customers he's catering to
are just pampered tourists!
The kind whose only concern
is posting on Fishbook.
Not customers who are looking
for a real experience.
He's attracting low-quality customers.
If that's the target market he wants
to cater to with his business,
that's his choice.
It's none of our business, sweetheart.
That's why he's boring.
Well, you know, sometimes,
boring is better.
Just think about everything
we've been through this past year.
I've met my quota.
I'd rather have a somewhat
boring life.
That's all.
So why did you choose me?
With all the complications in my life?
With my complicated past?
Sweetheart, what are you talking about?
Isn't that what you're trying to say?
That all I bring you is a headache?
That's not what I'm saying, sweetheart.
Even if you don't say it,
that's the truth.
That's how I feel.
Like I'm becoming exhausting to be around.
Oh, sweetheart.
You know, that's what's difficult
about you sometimes.
Your imagination goes off
in all directions,
and you read all kinds of meanings
into everything.
I don't regret choosing you.
Not at all.
At least I'm not boring!
Right?
Like this.
Chili with ice cream.
Do you think it makes sense
to put chili in ice cream?
It's not supposed to make sense,
but that's life.
You need something new every now and then.
You need a little adventure.
Not something boring,
not something that's always the same.
What?
I'm walking out, okay?
I know.
You're not going to stop me?
You're just going to let me leave?
You're cute.
Where are Mikoy and Chiara?
Is there no way to speed up
your internet connection?
The office's internet plan was downgraded
due to budget cuts.
And someone here
is hogging the internet
by illegally downloading
movies and series.
Here we go.
And today's topic is…
Let's say your airplane crashes.
So you need to do
everything you can to survive.
Let's go this way.
I hear something over here.
There.
Listen to your surroundings.
I can feel the vibration of the ground.
The sound is getting louder.
The shaking is getting stronger.
Mother Earth’s heartbeat.
Hey, what are you doing down there?
You might get hit by a coconut,
and you're trespassing here.
Sorry.
No wonder he has so many followers.
What does this have to do
with Mikoy and Chiara?
Just keep watching.
That brother is so grumpy.
It's not like his coconut is even good.
There.
So, guys, now we're going
to continue our search
for a body of water.
Because
if you listen carefully,
you can feel it in the ground
when you're close to a body of water.
Like a…
river.
Or a stream.
Or a river.
Are those the same thing? River?
Yes, they're the same.
River is just English.
There it is!
What a coincidence.
A river!
It's fresh!
I will teach you how to catch fish.
One more.
Got one!
Are you done having fun?
I thought you wanted to know what
really happened to Mikoy and Chiara.
Got you!
Look how big it is!
So, assuming you catch
a fish in the river, you're set!
You're good to go.
All you need to do
is find a way to cook the fish,
but if you can't,
just eat it raw!
Like sashimi.
Like sashimi, like in Japan.
-Rhamboy.
-Right?
-What are you doing?
-Aunt Tess.
I'm vlogging.
-What are you doing
-I tried…
with that enormous fish?
I tried catching fish
in the river earlier.
But it was too difficult,
so I just bought one as a prop.
Welcome to Sito Harong!
Life here is simple, but it's abundant.
Abundant.
Not because we have a lot of money.
It's abundant because
we're willing to share!
-Mommy Tess, Tito Mario, hello!
-Hey!
My boys!
Smelled the food.
Look at you!
Hi, guys! Hi, guys!
This is what you're good at!
Earlier, I needed people to carry things
and help set things up,
and you were nowhere to be found.
Now that there's nothing left to do,
-here you are.
-You saw the food, and here you are!
Right?
But I did clean the drainage canal.
You said you were brushing your teeth.
I said drainage canal.
How about the hole on our roof?
Isn't that your job?
Wait a minute!
So this is the new love team of the year!
Brother Mikoy and Chiara!
Come here, come here. Okay, okay.
Well, well, well!
Is this the one you caught in the river?
Oh, come on. That's what I've been saying.
Here's another one.
Maya-maya aren't caught in freshwater.
They're caught in saltwater.
-There!
-In the sea!
And to be honest,
I just bought this at the local market.
Right.
It's just really hard to catch fish.
I've already gone through Plan A, Plan B,
and this is already Plan C!
Yes.
Well, there are techniques for that.
Do you want me to teach you?
Wow!
Teach him? Really?
Don't!
Who knows what else
you might learn from Chiara?
Rhamboy, you won't just learn
how to catch fish from Chiara.
You'll also learn
how to catch Mikoy's heart.
-There you go!
-Wow!
Good one. My turn, my turn.
As for me, what I learned from Chiara
was how to keep gulping and gulping,
outdoing even the…
You're hilarious. You're hilarious.
All right, come on, everyone.
-Help me out, so we can get this done.
-Okay.
Chiara, you're good
at chopping vegetables, right?
-Come help me.
-Right, right. Come sit here.
You three, come here.
There's a list inside.
Get it. There's still some shopping to do.
Get the money from Mario. Hurry.
Uncle Mario!
Why me?
Of course. You're the head of the family,
aren't you?
With his profile,
we know that even though
he's just starting out,
he easily adapts to any situation.
Okay, if not because of being bored,
maybe because I feel like I’m stuck.
There you go!
I’m happy.
It’s just,
he seems like he doesn’t have a plan.
Plan about what?
You have to understand Chiara’s situation.
Think about the frustration
of being alone without your family.
But I’m here.
But it’s inevitable to feel
that she’s alone in this new life.
I have good news.
Something happened to Mikoy.
What?
He’s in the ecopark,
at the top of the mountain.
Chiara.
I’m coming, Mikoy.
What is happening to you?